Jamie Henry

Clermont, Florida, United States

sevenjrh@brighthouse.com



321 576-5440



linkedin.com/in/jamie-henry-8ba765154



https://jayhenry07.github.io/

Summary

I am a competitive and versatile graduate from the University of Central Florida with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering. I have a passion for computers, technology, video games and I enjoy problem solving and analyzing algorithms. I have experience in Unity, Full-Stack development, and multiple programming languages, such as the skills listed on my profile.

Experience

SMLLSTORM Full Stack Developer

SkillStorm

May 2022 - Present (2 months +)



Server

Olive Garden Sep 2021 - Apr 2022 (8 months)



Server

Feb 2016 - Sep 2021 (5 years 8 months)

Education



University of Central Florida

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering Aug 2019 - May 2022



Lake-Sumter State College

Associate's degree, General Studies Aug 2017 - May 2019

Licenses & Certifications



(A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - freeCodeCamp



Skills

JavaScript • Multitasking • Computer Engineering • Problem Solving • C (Programming Language) • Java • C# • Python (Programming Language) • Data Structures • Time Management

Honors & Awards



Mathematics Award - Lake-Sumter State College

Apr 2019

For academic excellence and achievement in mathematics.